<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Erik's Journal</title>
    <link>https://kartooner.com</link>
    <description>Personal journal entries from Erik Sagen</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 21:00:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Journal CMS</generator>
    
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Here we go again]]></title>
      <link>https://kartooner.com/entry/here-we-go-again.html</link>
      <guid>https://kartooner.com/entry/here-we-go-again.html</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[It's been awhile since I've written here. Long enough that I started to wonder if I'd ever come back to this.]]></description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It's been awhile since I've written here. Long enough that I started to wonder if I'd ever come back to this (blogging).</p>

<p>Life filled up. Work, kids, projects, distractions-a-plenty; stacking until writing slides further down the list. I'd open a blank page, stare at it, then close it again.</p>

<p>And yeah, I've written plenty elsewhere. Social platforms, group chats, quick-fire spots where everyone drops their thoughts these days. They work, but it never feels the same. Too fleeting. Too crowded. Too much ownership by others. Whereas writing here feels different, like putting words back where they belong.</p>

<p>In fact, it reminds me of the early 2000s, when blogging was everywhere and people were sharing just about anything. Sometimes polished, sometimes messy. But it was all out there, and that openness mattered.</p>

<p>So here I am again. No big declarations, no "content strategy", no promises of daily posts. Just... back. Writing when I can, how I can.</p>

<p>What you'll get here is what you've always gotten: pieces of life, half-thoughts, stories I don't want to lose, things that I'm still working out in real-time. Some will be short. Some long. Some will ramble and some will only make sense to me and that's more than okay.</p>

<p>Comments aren't working here yet, so if you feel like responding, we'll end up doing the ironic thing and take that back to the social platform.</p>

<p>P.S. If you're reading this, thanks for showing up. Feels good to show up again, too.</p>]]></content:encoded>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>